(Leonard:)I was unstoppable.
(Leonard:)I mean, I was...
I was on fire.
(Leonard:)It was like my mind and my body
were totally connected,
like-like athletes must feel
when they're in the zone.
(Penny:)Again, it was
miniature golf.
(Leonard:)Admit it, you're a
little turned on.
(Penny:)You can't be this proud.
(Leonard:)Why not?
(Penny:)Because I beat you.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hi.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good. You're back.
(Amy:)We have some
exciting news.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)As you know, Amy and I have
been together a long time,
(Sheldon:)and a lot of things
(Sheldon:)I never thought possible
now seem possible.
(Leonard:)Okay...
(Amy:)After a careful evaluation
of our relationship,
(Amy:)we decided that the time was
right to take a step forward.